Erik di Biase

Game Developer

London SE13 oberonx10@gmail.com 7504506395

Game developer, experienced with C++ and C# frameworks as well as game engines such as Unity and Unreal. Passionate about graphics, post-processing, and working with shaders in general using various graphics APIs like OpenGL, DirectX and Vulkan. Currently focusing on mobile AR development.

Work Experience

PASS Scheme Student

London Metropolitan University - London October 2016 to May 2018

As a PASS Student, my role focused on providing to first year students in my same course subject with help and guidance when developing their own projects. My help mostly consisted in debugging C++, JavaScript, OpenGL and DirectX projects and sharing my knowledge of coding standards, methodologies, OOP technics and version control tools which are essential for game developers.

Gameplay Programmer Intern

Objective-Z - London June 2017 to September 2017

My role in this Unity focused internship consisted in designing new innovative game mechanics, to be implemented in-game, providing the relative pitch documentation to my team leader, which if approved would be personally implemented by me and reviewed by my team leader.

Education

1st Class - BSc in Computer Games Programming

London Metropolitan University - London 2015 to 2018

Skills

C++, C#, OpenGL, DirectX, Unity, Unreal Engine, Javascript, Game Design, GLSL/HLSL, HTML/CSS, Augmented Reality, Virtual Reality

Links

http://www.erikdibiase.com

https://uk.linkedin.com/in/erikdibiase